A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Office Files of Lowell Hardin FA1528
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Agriculture Research and Training, 1968-1982; 1; 7.02 Cubic Feet 16 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
  - Program Strategy Records and Information Papers on Agricultural Programs, 1968-1982; 3
    - Consortium for International Development, Evaluation and Improvement of Basin Irrigation, Gideon Peri, Gaylord V. Skogerboe, and Donald I. Norum, Water Management Research Project, Colorado State University, Water Management Technical Report No. 49B, 1979 July (Box 16, Folder 122)
    - Consortium for International Development, Evaluation and Improvement of Border Irrigation, Gideon Peri, Donald I. Norum, and V. Skogerboe, Water Management Research Project, Colorado State University, Water Management Technical Report No. 49C, 1979 July (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Improving Irrigation Water Management on Farms - Annual Technical Report, Colorado State University, 1978 June (Box 17, Folder 124-125)
    - International Agricultural Research - Program/Budget Submissions of International Centers for 1979 and Related Materials, Ford Foundation Internal Review, 1978 October 25 (Box 17, Folder 126)
    - International Agricultural Research - Commentaries on the Work of the International Agricultural Research and Training Centers and their Program/Budget Submissions for 1980, Ford Foundation Internal Review, 1979 October 10 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    - Consortium for International Developments, Organizational Problems and Their Consequences on Improved Watercourses in Punjab, Ashfaq Hussain Mirza and Douglas James Merrey, Water Management Research Project, Colorado State University, Water Management Technical Report No. 55, 1979 December (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Improving Irrigation Water Management on Farms - Annual Technical Report, Colorado State University, 1979 June (Box 18, Folder 129-130)
    - Consortium for International Development, Farm Irrigation Constraints and Farmers' Responses: Comprehensive Field Survey in Pakistan, Max K. Lowdermilk, Alan C. Early and David M. Freeman, Water Management Research Project, Colorado State University, Water Management Technical Report No. 48-A, Volume I, 1978 September (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - Consortium for International Development, Organizational Alternatives to Improve On-Farm Water Management in Pakistan, Craig E. Radosevich and Craig Kirkwood, Colorado State University, Water Management Technical Report No. 36, 1975 June (Box 18, Folder 132)